<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Personae Labs</title>
    <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Personae Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:12:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://personaelabs.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Efficient ZK ECDSA (part 1)</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/efficient-ecdsa-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/efficient-ecdsa-1/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post of a 2 part series on our research improving private ECDSA signature verification, stemming from this ETHResearch post and implemented in this repository. In this post, we motivate our research and review our key insights. In the follow-up, we will provide a full security proof, discuss on-chain extensions, and introduce even faster implementations in proving systems like Halo2 and Nova.
Motivation ECDSA &amp;amp; ring signatures Client-side proving Key insights Take computation out of the SNARK Precomputing point multiples Off-chain verification To keccak or not to keccak Next up Appendix: half client &amp;amp; half server models Motivation ECDSA &amp;amp; ring signatures The Elliptic Curve Digital Signature Algorithm, or ECDSA for short, is a key tool in the identity layer of blockchains like Ethereum and Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In-person heyanon at SBC</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/sbcheyanon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/sbcheyanon/</guid>
      <description>The Science of Blockchain Conference (SBC) was held in early September at Stanford University. It was the first major conference since we had launched heyanon.xyz, which meant it was time to hack on an idea I&amp;rsquo;ve had for a while: in-person groups!
What&amp;rsquo;s heyanon? heyanon is an open-source app allowing users to anonymously tweet as a verified member of on and off-chain groups using ZKPs. In a world where users have to choose between the extremes of using their real-world identity or being fully pseudonymous, heyanon is working towards a future where you can select a subset of your identity and reputation to attach to your speech online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Personae Labs</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/personae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/personae/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Personae Labs, an R&amp;amp;D lab investigating the future of human expression online. We believe that the availability of advanced cryptography in consumer devices and the rise of public social networks will completely alter the shape of digital society.
Trend 1: publicly verifiable social networks Traditional digital social networks are not publicly verifiable. There’s no way to make a statement about your relationships in these networks that you know everyone will accept as true.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
