<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Personae Labs</title>
    <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Personae Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://personaelabs.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Spartan-ecdsa</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/spartan-ecdsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/spartan-ecdsa/</guid>
      <description>We introduce Spartan-ecdsa, which to our knowledge is the fastest open-source method to verify secp256k1 ECDSA signatures in zero-knowledge.
Right-field arithmetic Tricks from efficient-zk-ecdsa Benchmarks Public key group membership proof Ethereum address group membership proof Future work Speeding up Keccak On-chain verification Appendix 1: Under the hood Upstream dependencies Our implementations Appendix 2: Secp/Secq cycle in Sage Spartan-ecdsa is based on the Spartan Non-Interactive Zero-knowledge Proof (SpartanNIZK), which is a proving system in the Spartan zkSNARKs family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Efficient ECDSA &amp; the case for client-side proving</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/efficient-ecdsa-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/efficient-ecdsa-1/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we introduce our research improving private ECDSA signature verification, stemming from this ETHResearch post and implemented in this repository. We also introduce the importance of client-side proving to unlock the full potential of zero-knowledge cryptography.
There will be some math in this post! It might look scary! But the key insights of the method are simple and should teach you some fun cryptography.
Motivation ECDSA &amp;amp; ring signatures Client-side proving Notation Key insights Take computation out of the SNARK Precomputing point multiples Off-chain verification To keccak or not to keccak Next up Appendix: half client &amp;amp; half server models Elliptic curve interlude Proving setup Praise &amp;amp; criticism Looking to the future Motivation ECDSA &amp;amp; ring signatures Digital signatures are a key tool in public-key cryptography, where every user $u$ has a public key $pk_u$ and private key $sk_u$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In-person heyanon at SBC</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/sbcheyanon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/sbcheyanon/</guid>
      <description>The Science of Blockchain Conference (SBC) was held in early September at Stanford University. It was the first major conference since we had launched heyanon.xyz, which meant it was time to hack on an idea I&amp;rsquo;ve had for a while: in-person groups!
What&amp;rsquo;s heyanon? heyanon is an open-source app allowing users to anonymously tweet as a verified member of on and off-chain groups using ZKPs. In a world where users have to choose between the extremes of using their real-world identity or being fully pseudonymous, heyanon is working towards a future where you can select a subset of your identity and reputation to attach to your speech online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Personae Labs</title>
      <link>https://personaelabs.org/posts/personae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://personaelabs.org/posts/personae/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Personae Labs, an R&amp;amp;D lab investigating the future of human expression online. We believe that the availability of advanced cryptography in consumer devices and the rise of public social networks will completely alter the shape of digital society.
Trend 1: publicly verifiable social networks Traditional digital social networks are not publicly verifiable. There’s no way to make a statement about your relationships in these networks that you know everyone will accept as true.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
